freerealtime.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Statement - FreeRealTime.com

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

## _FreeRealTime.com Privacy Policy_

FreeRealTime.com respects your privacy. This statement of our Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from you and how we use that information. We consider the information you have shared with us strictly confidential and will use that information only as specified in this Privacy Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law. 

## Information We Gather and How We Use It

We collect certain information from you in order to provide you with the most interesting and useful Web site possible. 

We use your IP address to identify you, to gather demographic information that helps us understand how you and our other customers use our Web site, and to administer our Web site. If you purchase items through the MarketPlace, your IP address is used to help match you with your shopping cart. 

Our registration form requires you to give us contact information (like your name and email address), demographic information (like your zip code, age, occupation and income level) and profile information (like your investment experience). We use your contact information to contact you about our Web site and provide you with information and promotional material from our partners and advertisers. We use various other portions of your information to comply with New York Stock Exchange and Nasdaq Stock Market regulations regarding the distribution of real-time information, to target advertising, and to personalize our Web site by showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying the content according to your preferences. 

We sometimes conduct or sponsor surveys and contests on our Web site. If you elect to participate, we may ask you for contact, demographic and other information as part of these offerings. We would use this information to analyze and report on the results of surveys, to provide you with the results of the surveys and contests, and to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners and advertisers. Participation in surveys and contests is completely voluntary. 

From time to time we may supplement information that you provide to us with information received from third parties. 

## Information We May Disclose

We share demographic, profile and other general information about you and our other customers with our advertisers on an aggregate basis. This means that we tell our advertisers general information about the characteristics of our customer base such as how many female visitors and registered users we have within a certain postal code, but we do not specifically identify a particular female visitor or provide her contact information to our advertisers. 

Our advertisers may ask us to mail or e-mail you promotional information tailored to your interests. We will send you this information on behalf of our advertisers. From time to time we may use third parties (pursuant to a confidentiality agreement) to assist us in e-mail broadcasts and list management. You may opt-out of receiving these mailings as explained below under the heading “Your Options.” 

We may disclose your contact information or other specific information about you to third parties in conjunction with advertising, contests or new service offerings that you elect to participate in. 

We may share your contact information with our strategic partners and certain other companies. These selected entities may send you information by e-mail or regular mail, or may contact you by telephone. 

We may from time to time sell or transfer your contact and demographic information to affiliates and non-affiliates of the Company. 

As we continually look for ways to improve our business, we may buy or sell a company. If we buy or sell a business, the names collected will likely be transferred as a part of the sale. Information about registrants will be used in the aggregate. However, if we buy a business, we will honor the requests that customers made of that business regarding e-mail communications. In the event that we sell a business, we will do everything in our power to ensure that the e-mail communications requests you made of us are honored. 

We may release your contact and other information to third parties when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) cooperate with state and federal regulatory agency investigations, (iii) comply with the terms of the Subscriber Agreements with Nasdaq and the New York Stock Exchange, (iv) enforce the terms of our User Agreement or License Agreement, or (v) protect the rights of FreeRealTime.com or others. 

## Cookies

Our Web site uses “cookies” which deposit certain record keeping information in your hard drive. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, keep track of your preferences, deliver content specific to your interests, make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, keep track of your shopping cart and order status, and for other similar purposes. These cookies can't read other data from your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites or applications. 

Our Web site contains display ads sold by us or by outside advertising agencies. These ads may contain cookies which will be deposited in your hard drive if you click on the ads. Information generated from cookies deposited on your hard drive by our advertisers is collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. 

Most browsers are set to accept cookies unless you reconfigure your browser to refuse them or to notify you when you have received one. If you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of our site. 

## Subscriptions and Purchases

You may subscribe for a fee to certain services through our Web site or purchase publications and merchandise through the MarketPlace. If you subscribe for services which require payment of a fee or place an order with us through the MarketPlace, we will need your contact information and certain financial information such as your credit card number. Any financial information we collect will be used solely to bill you for the services and items you have purchased and to ship items to you. 

## Public Forums

Chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups are available to you through our Web site. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited responses. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any of your personal information in a public forum. 

## Security

Our Web site has certain security measures in place in effort to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our Web site contains links to other sites. FreeRealTime.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. You may wish to review the privacy policies of these sites. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**Third Party Cookies**   
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser. 

## Your Options

You may choose not to register for real-time quotes. Access to delayed quotes does not require registration. 

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and/or our partners. Your options include: 

* Opting to not receive promotional materials from our advertisers and/or,  

* Opting to not receive any newsletters, notices about new services or any other content from FreeRealTime.com. 

You may opt-out during the registration process or after registering by visiting us at <http://www.freerealtime.com/> and using the Account Information link or by contacting us [by e-mail](mailto:support@corp.freerealtime.com) Every e-mail we send to you will provide you with instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future e-mails. 

## Correct or Update Your Information

You may correct or update any information previously provided to us by visiting us at <http://www.freerealtime.com/> and using the Account Information link or by contacting us by [by e-mail](mailto:support@corp.freerealtime.com)

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Web Site Administrator  
FreeRealTime, LLC. href="/dl/frt/account?IM=support">Contact support 

## Additional Information

Please also refer to the FreeRealTime.com License Agreement for additional privacy related information. For general information about Internet privacy issues, you may wish to visit the Web site hosted by the Federal Trade Commission at <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy>. 

We may from time to time revise this Privacy Policy. This statement of our Privacy Policy was last revised on July 2, 2014.
